const nfpa211Chapter3QuizData = [
  {
    question: "'Approved' means it is acceptable to the ____________. (NFPA 211 3.2.1)",
    options: ["Homeowner", "Company", "Authority Having Jurisdiction", "Manufacturer"],
    answer: "Authority Having Jurisdiction"
  },
  {
    question: "__________ : An organization, office, or individual responsible for enforcing the requirements of a code or standard, or for approving equipment, materials and installation, or a procedure. (NFPA 211 3.2.2)",
    options: ["Manager/Lead", "IRC", "Authority Having Jurisdiction", "Qualified Agency"],
    answer: "Authority Having Jurisdiction"
  },
  {
    question: "__________ : Equipment or materials to which has been attached a label, symbol, or other identifying mark of an organization that is acceptable to the authority having jurisdiction and concerned with product evaluation, that maintains periodic inspection of production of labeled equipment or materials, and by whose labeling the manufacturer indicates compliance with appropriate standards or performance in a specified manner. (NFPA 211 3.2.3)",
    options: ["Identified", "Labeled", "Listed", "Approved"],
    answer: "Labeled"
  },
  {
    question: "__________ : Equipment, materials, or services included in a list published by an organization that is acceptable to the authority having jurisdiction and concerned with evaluation of products or services, that maintains periodic inspection of production of listed equipment or materials or periodic evaluation of services, and whose listing states that either the equipment, material, or service meets appropriate designated standards or has been tested and found suitable for a specified purpose. (NFPA 211 3.2.4)",
    options: ["Labeled", "Listed", "Published", "Approved"],
    answer: "Listed"
  },
  {
    question: "__________ : Indicates a mandatory requirement. (NFPA 211 3.2.5)",
    options: ["Approved", "Shall", "Should", "Recommended"],
    answer: "Shall"
  },
  {
    question: "__________ : Indicates a recommendation or that which is advised but not required. (NFPA 211 3.2.6)",
    options: ["Approved", "Shall", "Should", "Mandatory"],
    answer: "Should"
  },
  {
    question: "__________ : An NFPA standard, the main text of which contains only mandatory provisions using the word 'shall' to indicate requirements and that is in a form generally suitable for mandatory reference by another standard or code or for adoption into law. Nonmandatory provisions are not to be considered a part of the requirements of a standard and shall be located in appendix, annex, footnote, informational note, or other means as permitted in the NFPA manuals of style. When used in a generic sense, such as in the phrases 'standards development process' or 'standards development activites,' the term 'standards' includes all NFPA standards, including codes, standards, recommended practices, and guides. (NFPA 211 3.2.7)",
    options: ["Code", "Standard", "Recommendations", "Requirements"],
    answer: "Standard"
  },
  {
    question: "__________ : Capable of being exposed for inspection, maintenance, or repair without damage to the chimney or building structure of finish, but which might require the removal of doors, panels, or coverings using commonly available tools. (NFPA 211 3.3.1)",
    options: ["Readily Accessible", "Accessible", "Concealed (Inaccessible)", "Avaliable"],
    answer: "Accessible"
  },
  {
    question: "__________ : Exposed, or capable of being exposed, for operation, inspection, maintenance, or repair without the use of tools to open or remove doors, panels, or coverings. (NFPA 211 3.3.1.1)",
    options: ["Readily Accessible", "Accessible", "Non-Accessible", "Avaliable"],
    answer: "Readily Accessible"
  },
  {
    question: "__________ : Supplementary part or device added to an appliance to make it more useful, versatile, attractive and so forth. (NFPA 211 3.3.2)",
    options: ["Assistor", "Accessory", "Enhancement", "Appliance Sidekick"],
    answer: "Accessory"
  },
  {
    question: "Factory-Built Fireplace Accessories : Accessories intended for field installation into or attachment to factory-built and masonry fireplaces. (NFPA 211 3.3.2.1)",
    options: ["True", "False"],
    answer: "False"
  },
  {
    question: "Masonry Fireplace Accessories : Accessories intended for field installation into or attachment to masonry fireplaces. (NFPA 211 3.3.2.2)",
    options: ["True", "False"],
    answer: "True"
  },
  {
    question: "__________ : The air necessary to provide for the complet combustion of fuel and usually consisting of primary air, secondary air, and excess air. (NFPA 211 3.3.3.1)",
    options: ["Flue Gasses", "Combustion Air", "Carbon Monoxide", "Draft"],
    answer: "Combustion Air"
  },
  {
    question: "__________ : Any device that utilizes a fuel to produce light, heat, power, refrigeration, or air conditioning. (NFPA 211 3.3.4)",
    options: ["Fireplace", "Accessory", "Vent", "Appliance"],
    answer: "Combustion Air"
  },
  {
    question: "__________ : Appliances such as gas-operated coffee brewers and coffee urns and any appurtenant water-heating equipment, food and dish warmers, hot plates and griddles. (NFPA 211 3.3.4.1)",
    options: ["Direct Vent Appliance", "Building Heat Appliance", "Counter Appliance (Gas)", "Fuel-Burning Appliance"],
    answer: "Counter Appliance (Gas)"
  },
  {
    question: "__________ : A system consisting of an appliance, combustion air and flue gas connections between the appliance and the outside atmosphere, and a vent cap supplied by the manufacturer, and constructed so that all air for combustion is obtained from the outside atmosphere and all flue gases are discharged to the outside atmosphere. (NFPA 211 3.3.4.2)",
    options: ["Direct Vent Appliance", "Barometric Draft Regulator", "Counter Appliance (Gas)", "Automatic Electric Igniter"],
    answer: "Direct Vent Appliance"
  },
  {
    question: "__________ : A closed combustion pellet vent or chimney-connected solid pellet fuel-burning appliance incorporating a fuel-feed control mechanism. (NFPA 211 3.3.4.3.1)",
    options: ["Factory-Built Fireplace", "Boiler", "Gas Insert", "Pellet Fuel-Burning Appliance"],
    answer: "Pellet Fuel-Burning Appliance"
  },
  {
    question: "__________ : A chimney-connected device that burns solid fuel designed for purposes of heating, cooking, or both. (NFPA 211 3.3.4.3.2)",
    options: ["Solid Fuel-Burning Appliance", "Vented Appliance", "Counter Appliance (Gas)", "Pellet Fuel-Burning Appliance"],
    answer: "Solid Fuel-Burning Appliance"
  },
  {
    question: "__________ : A heating appliance designed specifically for installation in an attic or in a space with low headropm that normally is unoccupied. (NFPA 211 3.3.4.4.1)",
    options: ["Nonresidential, Medium-Heat Appliance", "Attic-Type Heating Appliance", "Free Standing Wood Stove", "Wood Burning Insert"],
    answer: "Attic-Type Heating Appliance"
  },
  {
    question: "A Building Heating Appliance is a Nonresidential, Low-Heat Appliance. (NFPA 211 3.3.4.4.2)",
    options: ["True", "False"],
    answer: "True"
  },
  {
    question: "__________ : Fuel-Burning appliances, not including high-pressure steam boilers, that are mainly used in residences but that might be used in other buildings and that do not produce continuous flue gas temperatures exceeding 1000°F. (NFPA 211 3.3.4.4.3)",
    options: ["Counter Appliance", "Residential-Type Heating Appliance", "Nonresidential, High-Heat Appliance", "Nonresidential, Medium-Heat-Appliance"],
    answer: "Residential-Type Heating Appliance"
  },
  {
    question: "Residential-Type Heating Appliances are meant for appliances that do not produce continuous flue gas temperatures exceeding 800°F. (NFPA 211 3.3.4.4.3)",
    options: ["True", "False"],
    answer: "False"
  },
  {
    question: "Heat-Producing Appliances produce heat by utilizing electric energy OR by burning fuel. (NFPA 211 3.3.4.5)",
    options: ["True", "False"],
    answer: "True"
  },
  {
    question: "__________ : A commercial, industrial, or institutional appliance needing a chimney capable of withstanding a continuous flue gas temperature not exceeding 1400°F. (NFPA 211 3.3.4.6)",
    options: ["Nonresidential, Low-Heat Appliance", "Nonresidential Appliance, 1400°F", "Nonresidential, High-Heat Appliance", "Nonresidential, Medium-Heat-Appliance"],
    answer: "Nonresidential Appliance, 1400°F"
  },
  {
    question: "__________ : A commercial, industrial, or institutional appliance needing a chimney capable of withstanding a continuous flue gas temperature exceeding 1800°F. (NFPA 211 3.3.4.7)",
    options: ["Nonresidential, Low-Heat Appliance", "Nonresidential Appliance, 1400°F", "Nonresidential, High-Heat Appliance", "Nonresidential, Medium-Heat-Appliance"],
    answer: "Nonresidential, High-Heat Appliance"
  },
  {
    question: "__________ : A commercial, industrial, or institutional appliance needing a chimney capable of withstanding a continuous flue gas temperature not exceeding 1000°F. (NFPA 211 3.3.4.8)",
    options: ["Nonresidential, Low-Heat Appliance", "Nonresidential Appliance, 1400°F", "Nonresidential, High-Heat Appliance", "Nonresidential, Medium-Heat-Appliance"],
    answer: "Nonresidential, Low-Heat Appliance"
  },
  {
    question: "__________ : A commercial, industrial, or institutional appliance needing a chimney capable of withstanding a continuous flue gas temperature not exceeding 1800°F. (NFPA 211 3.3.4.9)",
    options: ["Nonresidential, Low-Heat Appliance", "Nonresidential Appliance, 1400°F", "Nonresidential, High-Heat Appliance", "Nonresidential, Medium-Heat-Appliance"],
    answer: "Nonresidential, Medium-Heat Appliance"
  },
  {
    question: "__________ : An indirect-fired appliance provided with a flue collar to accommodate a venting system for conveying flue gases to the outside atmosphere. (NFPA 211 3.3.4.10)",
    options: ["Automatic Electic Igniter", "Open Masonry Fireplace", "Vented Appliance", "Factory-Built Chimney"],
    answer: "Vented Appliance"
  },
  {
    question: "__________ : An enclosure forming the outside of the appliance. (NFPA 211 3.3.5)",
    options: ["Chase", "Liner", "Appliance Casing (or Jacket)", "Baffle Plate"],
    answer: "Appliance Casing (or Jacket)"
  },
  {
    question: "__________ : The solid residue that remains after combustion is complete. (NFPA 211 3.3.8)",
    options: ["Ash", "Wood", "Creosote", "Baffle"],
    answer: "Ash"
  },
  {
    question: "__________ : A door below the grade level providing access to the ash receptacle. (NFPA 211 3.3.9)",
    options: ["Ash Receptacle Door", "Wash", "Vent", "Flue"],
    answer: "Ash Receptacle Door"
  },
  {
    question: "__________ : A device for fuel burners designed to utilize electric energy for ignition of a fuel-air mixture at the burner. (NFPA 211 3.3.11)",
    options: ["Boiler", "Automatic Electric Igniter", "Combustion", "Dilution Flue"],
    answer: "Automatic Electric Igniter"
  },
  {
    question: "__________ : A device built into a fuel-burning appliance, or made a part of a chimney connector or vent connector, that functions to reduce excessive draft through an appliance to a desired value by admitting ambient air into the appliance chimney, chimney connector, vent, or vent connector. (NFPA 211 3.3.13)",
    options: ["Damper", "Thimble", "Baffle", "Barometric Draft Regulator"],
    answer: "Barometric Draft Regulator"
  },
  {
    question: "__________ : A closed vessel in which water is heated, steam is generated, steam is superheated, or any combination thereof by the application of heat from combustible fuels in a self-contained or attached furnace. (NFPA 211 3.3.14)",
    options: ["Free Standing Wood Stove", "Gas Insert", "Boiler", "Duct Furnace"],
    answer: "Boiler"
  },
  {
    question: "__________ : A single boiler unit designed to burn more than one type of fuel (gas, oil, solid), either separately or simultaneously, using either separate or common combustion chambers and flues. (NFPA 211 3.3.14.1)",
    options: ["Supplementary Boiler", "Combination-Fuel Boiler", "Central Warm-Air Furnace", "Centeral Warm-Air, Gravity-Type Furnace"],
    answer: "Combination-Fuel Boiler"
  },
  {
    question: "__________ : A boiler for generating steam at guage pressures in excess of 15 psi, or for heating water to a temperature in excess of 250°F or at a gauge pressure in excess of 160 psi.. (NFPA 211 3.3.14.2)",
    options: ["Supplementary Boiler", "Combination-Fuel Boiler", "High-Pressure Boiler", "Low-Pressure Boiler"],
    answer: "High-Pressure Boiler"
  },
  {
    question: "__________ : A boiler for generating steam at guage pressures not in excess of 15 psi, or for furnishing water at a maximum temperature of 250°F at a maximum gauge pressure of 160 psi. (NFPA 211 3.3.14.3)",
    options: ["Supplementary Boiler", "Combination-Fuel Boiler", "High-Pressure Boiler", "Low-Pressure Boiler"],
    answer: "Low-Pressure Boiler"
  },
  {
    question: "__________ : A boiler, designed to burn one type of fuel (gas, oil, or solid), that is intended for supplementing a boiler burning another type of fuel (gas, oil, or solid) by means of a common heat transfer medium. (NFPA 211 3.3.14.4)",
    options: ["Supplementary Boiler", "Combination-Fuel Boiler", "Central Warm-Air Furnace", "Centeral Warm-Air, Gravity-Type Furnace"],
    answer: "Supplementary Boiler"
  },
  {
    question: "__________ : Where referring to bricklaying and masonry chimneys, that connection between brick, stone, or other masonry units formed by lapping them upon one another in carrying up the work, thereby forming an inseparable mass. (NFPA 211 3.3.15)",
    options: ["Join", "Bond", "Point of Contact", "Corbel"],
    answer: "Bond"
  },
  {
    question: "__________ : The conduit conveying flue gas from the appliance to the chimney. (NFPA 211 3.3.16)",
    options: ["Breeching", "Flue", "Flue Collar", "Draft Hood"],
    answer: "Bond"
  },
  {
    question: "__________ : The quantity of heat needed to raise the temperature of 1 pound of water 1°F. (NFPA 211 3.3.17)",
    options: ["BTU", "Force", "Thermal", "Temperature"],
    answer: "BTU"
  },
  {
    question: "What does BTU stand for? (NFPA 211 3.3.17)",
    options: ["British Technical Understanding", "Belgium Thermal Unit", "British Thermal Unit", "Brazilian Thermal Underlayment"],
    answer: "British Thermal Unit"
  },
  {
    question: "__________ : A protective covering or housing for the top of a chimney intended to prevent the entry of rain, snow, animals, and birds, and to prevent downdrafts. (NFPA 211 3.3.19.1)",
    options: ["Vent Cap", "Draft Hood", "Chimney Cap", "Spark Arrestor"],
    answer: "Chimney Cap"
  },
  {
    question: "__________ : A protective covering or housing attached to the vent termination, intended for preventing downdrafts and the entry of rain, snow, and animals. (NFPA 211 3.3.19.2)",
    options: ["Vent Cap", "Draft Hood", "Chimney Cap", "Spark Arrestor"],
    answer: "Vent Cap"
  },
  {
    question: "__________ : A structure containing one or more vertical or nearly vertical passageways for conveying flue gases to the outside atmosphere. (NFPA 211 3.3.29)",
    options: ["Flue", "Connector Pipe", "Chimney", "Heat Reclaimer"],
    answer: "Chimney"
  },
  {
    question: "__________ : A heating appliance chimney suitable for continuous use at 1000°F, composed of listed, factory-built components, designed for open, nonenclosed use at specified minimum clearances to combustibles, and assembled in accordance with the terms of the listing to form the completed chimney. (NFPA 211 3.3.29.1.1)",
    options: ["Factory-Built, Building Heating Appliance-Type Chimney", "Factory-Built 1400°F F-Type Chimney", "Masonry Chimney", "Factory-Built, Medium-Heat Appliance-Type Chimney"],
    answer: "Factory-Built, Building Heating Appliance-Type Chimney"
  },
  {
    question: "__________ : A chimney suitable for use at 1000°F, which complies with the 10 minute 1700°F temperature test of UL 103, and is composed of listed, factory-built components that might be fully enclosed in combustible, residential-type construction, and that is assembled in accordance with the terms of the listing to form a completed chimney. (NFPA 211 3.3.29.1.2)",
    options: ["Factory-Built, Building Heating Appliance-Type Chimney", "Factory-Built 1400°F F-Type Chimney", "Factory-Built, Residential-Type and Building Heating Appliance-Type Chimney", "Factory-Built, Medium-Heat Appliance-Type Chimney"],
    answer: "Factory-Built, Residential-Type and Building Heating Appliance-Type Chimney"
  },
  {
    question: "__________ : A residential type and building heating appliance chimney suitable for use at 1000°F, which complies with the optional 10 minute 2100°F temperature test of UL 103. Such chimneys are labeled as type HT and are required for certain solid fuel-fired applications. (NFPA 211 3.3.29.1.3)",
    options: ["Type HT Factory-Built, Residential-Type and/or Building Heating Appliance-Type Chimney", "Factory-Built 1400°F F-Type Chimney", "Factory-Built, Residential-Type and Building Heating Appliance-Type Chimney", "Factory-Built, Medium-Heat Appliance-Type Chimney"],
    answer: "Type HT Factory-Built, Residential-Type and/or Building Heating Appliance-Type Chimney"
  },
  {
    question: "__________ : A chimney suitable for continuous use at 1400°F, composed of listed, factory-built components, intended for open, nonenclosed use at specified minimum clearances to combustibles and for use in non combustible locations, and assembled in accordance with the terms of the listing to form the completed chimney. (NFPA 211 3.3.29.2)",
    options: ["Type HT Factory-Built, Residential-Type and/or Building Heating Appliance-Type Chimney", "Factory-Built 1400°F F-Type Chimney", "Factory-Built, Residential-Type and Building Heating Appliance-Type Chimney", "Factory-Built, Medium-Heat Appliance-Type Chimney"],
    answer: "Factory-Built 1400°F F-Type Chimney"
  },
  {
    question: "__________ : A chimney used with appliances that produce maximum flue gas temperatures of 1800°F, composed of listed, factory-built components, suitable for open, nonenclosed use at specified minimum clearances to combustibles, and assembled in accordance with the terms of the listing to form the completed chimney. (NFPA 211 3.3.29.3)",
    options: ["Type HT Factory-Built, Residential-Type and/or Building Heating Appliance-Type Chimney", "Factory-Built 1400°F F-Type Chimney", "Factory-Built, Residential-Type and Building Heating Appliance-Type Chimney", "Factory-Built, Medium-Heat Appliance-Type Chimney"],
    answer: "Factory-Built, Medium-Heat Appliance-Type Chimney"
  },
  {
    question: "__________ : A residential-type or building heating appliance chimney, or both, listed for use in positive internal pressure applications. (NFPA 211 3.3.29.4)",
    options: ["Factory-Built, Positive Pressure Capable Chimney", "Factory-Built, Negative Pressure Capable Chimney", "Low-Pressure Boiler", "Masonry Chimney"],
    answer: "Factory-Built, Positive Pressure Capable Chimney"
  },
  {
    question: "__________ : A field-constructed chimney of solid masonry units, bricks, stones, listed masonry chimney units, or reinforced Portland cement concrete, lined with suitable chimney flue liners. (NFPA 211 3.3.29.5)",
    options: ["Factory-Built, Positive Pressure Capable Chimney", "Factory-Built, Negative Pressure Capable Chimney", "Masonry Chimney", "Unlisted Metal Chimney"],
    answer: "Masonry Chimney"
  },
  {
    question: "__________ : A manufactured or field-constructed chimney intended only for nonresidential applications having one or more metal walls, or made of metal with a refractory lining, and that is capable of withstanding the flue gas conditions of its use. (NFPA 211 3.3.29.6)",
    options: ["Factory-Built, Positive Pressure Capable Chimney", "Factory-Built, Negative Pressure Capable Chimney", "Masonry Chimney", "Unlisted Metal (Smokestack) Chimney"],
    answer: "Unlisted Metal (Smokestack) Chimney"
  },
  {
    question: "__________ : A heat exchanger intended to be installed in a chimney connector between a heating appliance and the chimney to transfer heat from the flue gasses through metal to air or water. (NFPA 211 3.3.32)",
    options: ["Chimney Connector-Type Heat Reclaimer", "Dilution Flue", "Damper", "Radiant Room Heater"],
    answer: "Chimney Connector-Type Heat Reclaimer"
  },
  {
    question: "__________ : The lowest point of a flue within a chimney. (NFPA 211 3.3.34)",
    options: ["Smoke Shelf", "Throat", "Chimney Flue Base", "Flue Collar"],
    answer: "Chimney Flue Base"
  },
  {
    question: "__________ : An opening or hole in a chimney, usually located near its base, designed to allow access to the flue for purposes of removing ash, creosote, soot, and other extraneous matter that becomes trapped. (NFPA 211 3.3.37)",
    options: ["Ash Dump", "Damper", "Breech", "Cleanout Opening"],
    answer: "Cleanout Opening"
  },
  {
    question: "__________ : The distance between a heat-producing appliance, chimney, chimney connector, vent, vent connector, or plenum and other surfaces. (NFPA 211 3.3.38)",
    options: ["Requirements", "Clearance", "Accessible", "Standard"],
    answer: "Clearance"
  },
  {
    question: "__________ : A device used to dry wet laundry by means of heat derived from the combustion of fuel or from electric heating elements. (NFPA 211 3.3.39)",
    options: ["Air", "Fireplace", "Clothes Dryer", "Furnace"],
    answer: "Clothes Dryer"
  },
  {
    question: "__________ : A factory-built, mass produced dryer, primarily used in a family living environment. It might or might not be coin-operated for public use and usually is the smallest unit both physically and in function. (NFPA 211 3.3.39.1)",
    options: ["Boiler", "Fireplace", "Type 1 Clothes Dryer", "Type 2 Clothes Dryer"],
    answer: "Type 1 Clothes Dryer"
  },
  {
    question: "__________ : A factory-built, mass produced dryer used in a commercial business. It might or might not be operated by the public or a hired attendant. It might or might not be coin-operated and is not designed for use in an individual family living environment. It can be small, medium, or large in size. (NFPA 211 3.3.39.2)",
    options: ["Boiler", "Fireplace", "Type 1 Clothes Dryer", "Type 2 Clothes Dryer"],
    answer: "Type 2 Clothes Dryer"
  },
  {
    question: "__________ : A chemical process of oxidation that occurs at a rate fast enough to produce heat and usually light in the form of either a flow or flame. (NFPA 211 3.3.44)",
    options: ["Pyrolysis", "Drying", "Combustion", "Char"],
    answer: "Combustion"
  },
  {
    question: "__________ : Constituents resulting from the combustion of a fuel with oxygen of the air, including the inert but excluding excess air. (NFPA 211 3.3.46)",
    options: ["Combustion", "Combustion Products", "Pressure", "Refractory Products"],
    answer: "Combustion Products"
  },
  {
    question: "__________ : Not capable of being exposed for inspection, maintenance, or repair without damage to the chimney, building structure, or finished surfaces; without removal of permanently attached parts of the building; or without special tools. (NFPA 211 3.3.48)",
    options: ["Readily Accessible", "Accessible", "Concealed (Inaccessible)", "Barely Accessible"],
    answer: "Concealed (Inaccessible)"
  },
  {
    question: "__________ : The pipe that connects a fuel-burning appliance to a chimney. (NFPA 211 3.3.49.1)",
    options: ["Flue", "Liner", "Chimney Connector", "Vent Connector"],
    answer: "Chimney Connector"
  },
  {
    question: "__________ : The pipe that connects a fuel-burning appliance to a gas vent or Type L vent. (NFPA 211 3.3.49.2)",
    options: ["Flue", "Liner", "Chimney Connector", "Vent Connector"],
    answer: "Vent Connector"
  },
  {
    question: "__________ : Units of masonry projecting from or projecting upward and outward from the face of a wall or chimney in courses to form a support or ledge for a beam, rafter, or other member. (NFPA 211 3.3.50)",
    options: ["Corbel", "Supporting Brick", "Lintel", "Structural Wall"],
    answer: "Corbel"
  },
  {
    question: "__________ : A sloped covering for the top of a masonry chimney that is designed to shed water away from the flue liner and the chimney and to allow expansion and movement of the flue liner. (NFPA 211 3.3.52)",
    options: ["Chimney Cap", "Waterproofing Application", "Crown", "Spall"],
    answer: "Crown"
  },
  {
    question: "__________ : A valve or plate for controlling draft or the flow of gases, including air. (NFPA 211 3.3.53)",
    options: ["Draft Hood", "Damper", "Catalytic Converter", "Baffle Board"],
    answer: "Damper"
  },
  {
    question: "__________ : A damper operated by an automatic control. (NFPA 211 3.3.53.1)",
    options: ["Manually Operated Damper", "Automatically Operated Damper", "Flue Gas Damper", "Throat"],
    answer: "Automatically Operated Damper"
  },
  {
    question: "__________ : A damper located on the downstream side of the combustion chamber of a fuel-burning appliance, usually in a flue passage of the appliance or in the chimney or vent connector. (NFPA 211 3.3.53.2)",
    options: ["Manually Operated Damper", "Automatically Operated Damper", "Flue Gas Damper", "Throat"],
    answer: "Flue Gas Damper"
  },
  {
    question: "__________ : An adjustable damper manually set an locked in the desired position. (NFPA 211 3.3.53.3)",
    options: ["Manually Operated Damper", "Automatically Operated Damper", "Flue Gas Damper", "Throat"],
    answer: "Manually Operated Damper"
  },
  {
    question: "__________ : A pressure difference that causes gases or air to flow through a chimney, vent, flue, or appliance. (NFPA 211 3.3.57)",
    options: ["Flow", "Biometric Damper", "Draft", "Thermodynamics"],
    answer: "Draft"
  },
  {
    question: "__________ : Draft produced by a fan or an air or steam jet. (NFPA 211 3.3.57.1)",
    options: ["Mechanical Flow", "Mechanical Draft", "Natural Draft", "Natural Flow"],
    answer: "Mechanical Draft"
  },
  {
    question: "__________ : Draft produced by the difference in the weight of a column of flue gases within a chimney or vent system and a coresponding column of air of equal dimension outside the chimney or venting system. (NFPA 211 3.3.57.2)",
    options: ["Mechanical Flow", "Mechanical Draft", "Natural Draft", "Natural Flow"],
    answer: "Natural Draft"
  },
  {
    question: "__________ : A nonadjustable device built into an appliance, or made a part of the vent connector from an appliance, that is designed to (1) provide for the ready escape of the flue gases from the appliance in the event of no draft, back-draft, or stoppage beyond the draft hood, (2) prevent a back-draft from entering the appliance, and (3) neutralize the effect of stack action of the chimney or gas vent upon the operation of the appliance. (NFPA 211 3.3.58)",
    options: ["Draft Hood", "Flue Collar", "Chimney Cap", "Top Mount Damper"],
    answer: "Draft Hood"
  },
];

if (!window.quizRegistry) window.quizRegistry = {};
window.quizRegistry['NFPA 211 - Chapter 3: Definitions'] = nfpa211Chapter3QuizData;